当你用橡皮筋练习 Dogs eat bones，并搭建自己的
When you used the rubber band with dogs eat bones, and when you built your own
句子时，你已经看到语调会弱化非重读词。语调是
sentence, you saw that intonation reduces the unstressed words. Intonation is the
峰，弱化音是谷。刚开始时，你应该制造额外高的
peak, and reduced sounds are the valleys. In the beginning, you should make extra
高峰之间有长而深的谷。拿不准时，就弱化。
high peaks in long, deep valleys. When you're not sure, reduce. In the following
练习时要带着这个想法。冠词、介词、代词这类小词，
exercise, work with this idea. Small words such as articles, prepositions, pronouns,
连词、关系代词和助动词都会被轻轻带过，
conjunctions, relative pronouns, and auxiliary verbs are lightly skimmed over
几乎不发出来。你已经看过语调如何改变词和句子的意思。
and almost not pronounced. You've seen how intonation changes the meaning in words
在单音节词内部，它区分词尾是有声辅音还是无声辅音，
and sentences. Inside a one-syllable word, it distinguishes between a final-voiced or
比如 bad 和 bet。在更长的词里，比如 unique 与 unique，
unvoiced consonant, bad and bet. Inside a longer word, unique versus unique, the
发音和意义会在词汇层面发生变化。在句子里，he seems
pronunciation and meaning change in terms of vocabulary. In a sentence, he seems
nice 与 he seems nice 的意义会在意图层面发生变化。在句子中，
nice, he seems nice, the meaning changes in terms of intent. In a sentence,
语调也能让一个清楚的元音消失。
intonation can also make a clear vowel sound disappear. When a vowel is stressed,
重读时，元音会有特定声音；不重读时，通常听起来像 UH，
it has a certain sound. When it's not stressed, it usually sounds like UH,
to、at、as 这类小词通常不重读，所以其中的元音
pronounced uh. Small words like to, at, or as are not usually stressed, so the vowel
元音就会消失。
disappears.